gamerzplanet.net 2008-12-18

# GamerzPlanet Privacy Policy - GamerzPlanet - For All Your Online Gaming Needs!!

01-17-2007, 02:37 PM  |    #[ **1**](http://www.gamerzplanet.net/forums/gamerzplanet-discussion/100304-gamerzplanet-privacy-policy.html#post622214 "permalink")  
  
Head Admin of GzP

Last Online: Today 09:13 AM

Join Date: Nov 2005

Location: Canada

Age: 21

Posts: 8,006 

Thanks: 55

Thanked 1,165 Times in 386 Posts 

iTrader: **[0](http://www.gamerzplanet.net/forums/itrader.php?u=6)** / 0% 

Points: 242,802.52

Bank: 144,553.73

Total Points: 387,356.25

| 

**GamerzPlanet Privacy Policy**

* * *

**Privacy Policy  
  
**

**Our Commitment To Privacy** Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.   
  
**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the GamerzPlanet website. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name   

  * Address   

  * Email address
  * (etc.) 

**The Way We Use Information:** Your information will only be used to make GamerzPlanet a better place for all people. We only use information that will not be able to identify individual such as age, and country. **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by sending us an e-mail. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

Finally, we never use personally identifiable information to third parties without your permission.

**How To Contact Us**

We reserve the right to modify and amend these terms at any time without notice. If you have any concerns on about GamerzPlanet Privacy Police, please [Contact Us.](http://www.gamerzplanet.net/forums/sendmessage.html)  

__________________

 ** Want a more friendly and fun message board? Come join us at ******[Only registered and activated users can see links.[](http://www.gamerzplanet.net/forums/register.php)]** **

**GzP Recruiting Coders for Combat Arms** \- **[Only registered and activated users can see links.[](http://www.gamerzplanet.net/forums/register.php)]**  
  
  |
